[{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981709721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":23556,"timeElapsed":35127},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981713224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3494,"timeElapsed":38630},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981717607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4371,"timeElapsed":43013},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981720516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2896,"timeElapsed":45922},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981725083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4558,"timeElapsed":50490},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981728743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3650,"timeElapsed":54150},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981732689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3934,"timeElapsed":58096},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981737363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4661,"timeElapsed":62769},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981740524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":65930},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981754299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":12315,"timeElapsed":79705},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981759616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5304,"timeElapsed":85022},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981763017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":3391,"timeElapsed":88424},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981765205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2178,"timeElapsed":90611},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981769986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4771,"timeElapsed":95393},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981772988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2992,"timeElapsed":98394},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981776341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":101747},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981778893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2541,"timeElapsed":104299},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981785607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6703,"timeElapsed":111013},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981796000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8929,"timeElapsed":121407},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981798171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2162,"timeElapsed":123578},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981801880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3701,"timeElapsed":127287},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981808058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":6169,"timeElapsed":133465},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981816620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8551,"timeElapsed":142027},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981825762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9133,"timeElapsed":151169},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981828841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3072,"timeElapsed":154248},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981831221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2371,"timeElapsed":156627},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981834178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2947,"timeElapsed":159584},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981844364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8702,"timeElapsed":169770},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981846648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2272,"timeElapsed":172054},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981850112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3453,"timeElapsed":175518},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981852772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2652,"timeElapsed":178179},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981855203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2420,"timeElapsed":180610},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981857990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2780,"timeElapsed":183397},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981860354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2357,"timeElapsed":185761},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981862842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2480,"timeElapsed":188249},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981865183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2330,"timeElapsed":190589},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981893043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":26828,"timeElapsed":218450},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981896217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3163,"timeElapsed":221623},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981905905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9677,"timeElapsed":231311},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981909676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3760,"timeElapsed":235083},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981919168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9480,"timeElapsed":244575},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981922944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3767,"timeElapsed":248351},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981931603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":8649,"timeElapsed":257010},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981934764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3152,"timeElapsed":260170},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981939301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4528,"timeElapsed":264707},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981953357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12393,"timeElapsed":278763},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981963967,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":10604,"timeElapsed":289374},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981968099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4123,"timeElapsed":293506},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981976003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7894,"timeElapsed":301410},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981980968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4955,"timeElapsed":306375},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981983467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2488,"timeElapsed":308873},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981989530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6053,"timeElapsed":314936},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981993380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3837,"timeElapsed":318786},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981996666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3275,"timeElapsed":322073},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982007691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9083,"timeElapsed":333097},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982010256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2558,"timeElapsed":335663},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982018156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7893,"timeElapsed":343563},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982021304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3139,"timeElapsed":346710},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982024675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3361,"timeElapsed":350081},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982028588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3905,"timeElapsed":353995},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982030945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2349,"timeElapsed":356352},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982034919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":360326},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982037166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":362573},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982050167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":11091,"timeElapsed":375573},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982055664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5487,"timeElapsed":381071},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982058147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":383554},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982069202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":11044,"timeElapsed":394609},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982090959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":21746,"timeElapsed":416366},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982095811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4843,"timeElapsed":421217},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982098532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":2713,"timeElapsed":423938},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982108582,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10040,"timeElapsed":433989},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982113007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4416,"timeElapsed":438414},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982116247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3229,"timeElapsed":441653},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982124282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6929,"timeElapsed":449688},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982126901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":452307},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982134226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7316,"timeElapsed":459633},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982159902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":25666,"timeElapsed":485309},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982165282,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5368,"timeElapsed":490688},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982170464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5174,"timeElapsed":495871},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982174242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":499648},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982177740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3488,"timeElapsed":503147},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982180244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2493,"timeElapsed":505650},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982183351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3097,"timeElapsed":508758},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982195450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":10949,"timeElapsed":520856},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982207797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":12341,"timeElapsed":533204},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982222358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":14550,"timeElapsed":547764},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982228702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":6336,"timeElapsed":554109},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982238995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10285,"timeElapsed":564401},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982242221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3220,"timeElapsed":567628},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982244842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2613,"timeElapsed":570249},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982246555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1702,"timeElapsed":571962},{"subjectID":"m0erkpo4lc","prolificID":"672628f1dd186b536530f278","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22fd866dab65bf943bf","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734982248527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1961,"timeElapsed":573934}]